rocketway.net 2019-07-16

# This Website contains links to other websites operated by third parties. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the

PRIVACY POLICY
The purpose of this Policy is to let you know what information
we collect, how we collect it, and under what circumstances we
use it. By visiting our Website (www.rocketway.net), you are
accepting the practices described in this Policy. We keep us in
processing your data to the Dutch Data Protection Act (Wet
bescherming persoonsgegevens). In this Privacy Policy we
explain what information we collect and use and for what
purpose. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please
do not use the Website.
INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU
We collect information you directly give us. For example, we
collect information about you when you sign up for our
Newsletter, give feedback, request customer support or
otherwise communicate with us. The information we receive
from customers is stored on our server. This personal
information is not shared with any third party, however from
time to time we may correspond with you with regard to any
information or updates that may be of interest to you.
NEWSLETTER SUBSCRIPTSION
Users who sign up for our email newsletter will find that
address in safe hands. Your email is only stored so we can
send you the newsletter. It’s never used for other purposes, or
shared with third parties. we collect and store all of the
following information that you provide: name, email address. If
you email us at support@rocketway.net or choose to
unsubscribe from our Newsletter your email will be removed
from our system.
THIRD PARTY SITES
This Website contains links to other websites operated by third
parties. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the

personal information that we collect through this website and
we cannot be responsible for personal information that third
parties may collect, store, and use through their website. You
should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit
carefully.
CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not
reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your
consent.
COMPANY DETAILS
Sebastian Groenendaal
Registered Office: Koekoeksbloem 2, 1422 KP Uithoorn, The
Netherlands
Chamber of Commerce, Uithoorn, nr. 57597669
VAT nr. NL1961.85.300.B01
E-mail: bas@rocketway.net
Van Dijk Grafisch Ontwerp
Registered Office: Frida Katz-Erf 256, 3315 VP, Dordrecht
Chamber of Commerce, Dordrecht, nr. 24434838
VAT nr. NL1799.49.068.B01
E-mail: steve@rocketway.net
